So Anuj ji, as a mid cap funda, we have selected
ICICI Labrad, a private sector company engaged in non-life general insurance. On the
basis of fundamentals,
Anuj bhai, for a long time, our opinion has been to
invest in ICICI Labrador. The
downside risks seem to be very low from the level at which it is operating
and from a long term perspective,
they seem to be very low and
from a long term perspective, a positive trend will
emerge on the basis of data, this is what we
believe.  Not by using full force but
start from this level and keep adding on the decline.
Gaurav ji is liking ICICI LB DA Mid Cap Fund.
Buying advice
at these levels A recap of four of four we
started with cheap option from Chandan ji
in cheap option of cements and
continuously at these levels.  Well, there
is a good boom in the market.  But there are some counters
that are working on the backfoot.  One of them
is Industar.  Please keep Industar
on your screen once.  But this counter is among the top losers in futures
and the reason for this is a
downgrade.